gameshed.com 2018-06-22

# Privacy and Copyright Compliance Policy

If you`re reading this, it`s because you want to know: 

  * What information we are collecting on www.gameshed.com
  * What we`re doing with the information we collect.
  * What your options are related to the information we collect

This Privacy Policy applies to the GAMESHED website located at www.gameshed.com

By accessing the Site, you agree to and accept this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective as of May 11, 2018. In the future, our Site may change, and if appropriate, we will revise this Privacy Policy to reflect the changes, and you agree that the information we collect will be subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time we collect that information. We`ll post the updated version here and may contact you with notices concerning our Privacy Policy. In addition, we suggest that you review this Privacy Policy periodically, as it may be updated from time to time.

**Information We Collect**

**Information You Provide on Site**

You provide non-personally identifiable information such as your unique username to GAMESHED when choosing to create an account or to participate in various activities on the Site such as chat or posting messages in the games comment section. 

You may choose to disclose personal information about yourself in our online chat rooms, game comments or in creating user "profiles" and filling the "About You / Mini Profile Description" fields. Information that you disclose in these areas is public information, and will be accessible to anyone who uses our Site. However, you may choose to have your profile page be public or private. In the case where you chose to make your profile page private, the information there (including unlocked badges, "favorite games" list, "my friends" list, etc.) will only be visible to you.

**Site Information We Track**

The Site uses passive tracking technologies to log information such as IP address, browser type, pages visited, and Site usage (for example: what pages are accessed, how often, referring/exit pages and URLs). We may also employ "cookies" or similar technologies such as web beacons or match scripts that provide additional functionality to the Site and help us analyze Site usage more accurately. You can set your browser to reject cookies, but if you do, some features on our Site will not function normally.

When you visit our Website, our server automatically save your computer`s IP address. IP addresses will be collected, along with information about the actual web pages that you visit on the Website. If you arrive at the Website via a link from another website, the URL of the linking website and the URL of any website that you link to next will also be collected.

We use Google Analytics to automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. This data is stored in files called web logs. These web logs may include information such as your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the site you came from, the next site you visit and cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

None of the data collected through web beacons, cookies, Flash cookies or web log data provides us with any personal information about you. We use this data on an aggregated basis to analyze how our users are interacting with the site and to customize your experience. If you are logged in to the site, we could associate information about your site usage that is collected by cookies, web beacons and web logs with your user account. However, we don`t do this on an individual basis other than in cases of suspected abuse or illegal behavior. See our policy below about Investigating Abuse.

**Cookies**

In addition, we store certain information from your browser, using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user`s computer and is tied to information about the user. Our website may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to enhance and personalize your experience on the Website, including the following: 

  * to operate and improve offerings on the Website;
  * to help authenticate you when you are on the Website;
  * to remember your preferences and registration information, as applicable;
  * to customize the content and advertisements provided to you through the Website.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you can (re)set your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. You can opt out of receiving cookies from certain third-party advertising networks by resetting your browser. You may also use the following link to the Network Advertising Initiatives cookies [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices) or the link to the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance (EDAA) [opt-out page](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/). However, some features and services may not function properly if cookies are disabled.

**Do Not Track**

Do Not Track (DNT) is a privacy preference that users can set in their web browsers allowing users to opt out of tracking by websites and online services. At the present time, the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) has not yet established universal standards for recognizable DNT signals, and, therefore, GameShed.com does not recognize DNT. 

**Flash Cookies**

The Flash content on this site may contain Flash cookies put in place by the developers. These are used to store game save data and serve third party ads. We are not responsible for the use of these Flash cookies and do not share data with them. 

**Third Party Advertising**

GAMESHED may also use ad network providers to help present advertisements on the Website. These ad network providers use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to help the presenting, better targeting, and measuring of the effectiveness of their advertisements, using data gathered over time and across their networks of web pages to determine or predict the characteristics and preferences of their audiences. 

GAMESHED has integrated Google AdSense. Google AdSense is an online service which allows the placement of advertising on third-party sites. Google AdSense is based on an algorithm that selects advertisements displayed on third-party sites to match with the content of the respective third-party site. Google AdSense allows an interest-based targeting of the Internet user, which is implemented by means of generating individual user profiles.

The operating company of Google`s AdSense component is Alphabet Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Pkwy, Mountain View, CA 94043-1351, United States.

The purpose of Google`s AdSense component is the integration of advertisements on our website. Google AdSense places a cookie on the information technology system of the data subject. The definition of cookies is explained above. With the setting of the cookie, Alphabet Inc. is enabled to analyze the use of our website. With each call-up to one of the individual pages of this Internet site, which is operated by the controller and into which a Google AdSense component is integrated, the Internet browser on the information technology system of the data subject will automatically submit data through the Google AdSense component for the purpose of online advertising and the settlement of commissions to Alphabet Inc. During the course of this technical procedure, the enterprise Alphabet Inc. gains knowledge of personal data, such as the IP address of the data subject, which serves Alphabet Inc., inter alia, to understand the origin of visitors and clicks and subsequently create commission settlements.

The data subject may, as stated above, prevent the setting of cookies through our website at any time by means of a corresponding adjustment of the web browser used and thus permanently deny the setting of cookies. Such an adjustment to the Internet browser used would also prevent Alphabet Inc. from setting a cookie on the information technology system of the data subject. Additionally, cookies already in use by Alphabet Inc. may be deleted at any time via a web browser or other software programs.

Furthermore, Google AdSense also uses so-called tracking pixels. A tracking pixel is a miniature graphic that is embedded in web pages to enable a log file recording and a log file analysis through which a statistical analysis may be performed. Based on the embedded tracking pixels, Alphabet Inc. is able to determine if and when a website was opened by a data subject, and which links were clicked on by the data subject. Tracking pixels serve, inter alia, to analyze the flow of visitors on a website.

Through Google AdSense, personal data and information-which also includes the IP address, and is necessary for the collection and accounting of the displayed advertisements-is transmitted to Alphabet Inc. in the United States of America. These personal data will be stored and processed in the United States of America. The Alphabet Inc. may disclose the collected personal data through this technical procedure to third parties.

Google AdSense is further explained under the following link <https://www.google.com/intl/en/adsense/start/>

**How to manage cookies**

You can do so by adapting your browser settings. You can choose to block cookies or to accept only cookies from specific websites.

Below, you will find an overview of the possibilities the browsers offer to manage cookies.

**Google Chrome:** Open your browser. Click the Chrome menu and choose settings. Click display advanced settings and then the button Settings for content in the `Privacy` section. In the `Cookies` section you can edit your cookies settings and remove cookies.

**Internet Explorer:** Open your browser. Click Tools and then Internet options. Click the `Privacy` section and choose the level you want with the slide control. You can also change this manually by clicking Advanced. A distinction is made between permanent direct cookies (first party cookies), permanent indirect cookies (third party cookies) and temporary cookies (session cookies). You can remove cookies by means of the main screen of internet options.

**Mozilla Firefox:** Open your browser. Select Privacy. Set Firefox to Use adapted settings for history. To switch cookies on, put a checkmark with Accept cookies of websites. To switch off cookies, remove this checkmark. Firefox also gives you the possibility to switch off cookies of third parties (third party cookies). Furthermore you can set for how long cookies can be kept. Click Show cookies and you can remove one or several cookies.

**Safari:** Open your browser. In Safari, cookie administration is limited to one screen. In tab sheet Preferences click Privacy. You then have three possibilities to accept cookies. Via Show Cookies you can also remove cookies.

**Opera:** Open your browser. Click the Extra menu and then Preferences. Via Advanced and Cookies you can set your cookies settings. You also have the possibility to have new cookies removed automatically when you close each Internet session. Moreover, you can decide about each cookie that is sent to your computer. You do this by clicking Ask me before accepting cookies. Each time a site wants to save a cookie, a dialog box is displayed.

**Registration Form**

Our site`s registration form requires users to give us a unique identifier such as a username for use as account numbers in our record system. _We DO NOT require any personally identifiable information from our users when they create an account on our website._

**How We Use This Information**

We use your non-personally identifiable Site usage data to improve the quality and design of the Site and to provide personalized services and recommendations to our users. 

**Children**

This Site is offered and made available only to users sixteen (16) years of age or older. If you are not yet 16 years old or the required greater age for certain features please discontinue using the Site immediately. We do not knowingly collect information for any child under the age of 16. If you are the parent of a child under the age of 16 and have a concern regarding your child`s information on our Services, please contact us at   
_contact[@]gameshed.com_ (replace the [@] with @ before send us an email) 

**How To contact us**

If you have questions or requests regarding our privacy practices, please contact us at: contact[@]gameshed.com (replace the [@] with @ before send us an email)
